Sean de Groot

Web Developer

Kitchener-Waterloo

✓ degroot.sd@gmail.com

seandegroot.com

in Sean de Groot

<u>seandaniel</u>

About

A web developer who has a passion for progressive technology, and well-designed products that provide meaningful solutions. My past work experience focused on improving a complex irrigation system through scalable components, followed by an intricate plan. With my technical and problem-solving skills, I can provide a product that meets the consumers' expectations.

Skills

HTML5 React Git Collaboration Web Accessibility CSS3 jQuery API Integrations SEO Practices

JavaScript Firebase Photoshop Conversions Cross-Browser Testing
Sass Gulp Responsive Design Peer Code Reviews

Education

Juno College of Technology | 2019 - 2020

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp | JavaScript Fundamentals | Web Development Fundamentals

Projects

The Specific Press - React / Sass / The News API

In today's world, it's important to stay in the know. Fetching thousands of up-to-date articles courtesy of The News API, this React app features a smooth browser and device consistency, all under a clean user interface.

Verbeek's Farm and Garden Centre - HTML5 / Sass / jQuery

Verbeek's services everyone from the home gardener to the largest farm properties across their residing county. Built and designed through Sass partials with the demographic in mind, conveying the business's information precisely.

Experience

Mentor - Juno College of Technology | July 2020 - present

• Communicates between shared screens, guiding students' through technical problems and writing clean HTML, CSS and JavaScript code.

Foreman, Irrigation Technician - Shannon Lake Golf Course | 2018 - 2019

- Installed modular irrigation layouts following a detailed plan, documenting the process and outcome.
- Delicately troubleshot over 5100 metres of irrigation line with modern techniques.
- Analyzed and adjusted irrigation schedules to maximize the capacity and efficiency of water flow.
- Meticulously led a crew of a dozen individuals in grooming the golf course into daily pristine shape.